Hello Hello friends, how are you watching
another State Support YouTube channel,
so before starting today's video,
I want to tell you that first of all
you should subscribe to our channel, your YouTube channel,
then
what will happen by subscribing, you will keep
getting all the updates of our channel videos on time and by
pressing the next bell icon and clicking on it,
what will happen by this, you will keep getting all the video
notifications on your phone while sitting at home, what will happen by this,
you will keep getting updates of
all the fields Prince related to LIC and Star Health from our channel while
sitting at home, if you
click on it, then let's start today's video
and friends, how are you
madam, I welcome you all to my Deposit Insurance Tech Support
YouTube channel,
friend, in front of you is the Star Health app, I
want to tell you something about the Plan Family Health Optima Plan, in
which you
can take this plan for people from 18 years to 70 years
and if you have children from zero years to 35 years, then
with time and
you can take this policy with husband-wife mode three children, the
specialty in this plan  What is your doubt? If
you take a plan of 5 lakhs,
then the entire family means two plus three lakhs,
plus wife and three children,
everyone will get a liability of six and a half inches on height context five.
Along with this, if you
want to take half the hospitalization cash benefit, then this is also available to people.
Secondly,
today IRDA has notified that if
you have taken help from any company and
if you want, that is, you are not satisfied with that company, be it
Reliance, Tata,
Bajaj, Left or Max Bupa or all the
health plans
running in the horoscope sector, if you
look at them, then also there is Star Health Issues Arrest
or what to say in India,
it is being measured at the first place in the world, that is,
more than 50,000, which means that the
clip is attached with the hospital.
Secondly, the
number one bowler in the England team is sitting on the list of
friends, we do
Anuj saving for everyday, there are
two types of savings, one is different from the other
that  Today we invest and when the time is up,
we take that money and spend it somewhere
else. This was a saving
plan but no one knows about health,
like nowadays you are seeing that
since March,
compared to the Corona epidemic that we are going through,
how much has it cost in that, that
this incident must have happened with some lizard, our
loved ones must have known about it,
so we see small diseases,
dengue, typhoid, if all this happens then we go
to the hospital, then it does not matter, but it
costs a
minimum of 3 lakhs, maximum limit 5 lakhs and
here you
get a lot of facilities, that is,
Akshay is corrupt in it, you get inside
ambulance care, room care, apart from this, that means
somewhere, which is one person in a footer,
if we
want to go to another city by plane
for treatment, especially in Patna, its
44, that chapter of it is attached with it,
your topper topper is very special in this, the garden is done,
help is done, Shri Ram is done, horn is done like this,
still this is what scene s  It happened, I passed, it was
a coincidence, it happened, there was a lot of
meaning, the topper, topper health, topper
hospital is tagged with half hospitals,
friends, do watch and you can watch our
Insurance Tech Support YouTube channel,
subscribe and if
you need some special information then while watching our channel,
comment and
you will be given the correct information or guidance,
thank you
Jhal